Finding Aid for Edward Raymond Turner pamphlets and reprints
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Edward Raymond Turner pamphlets and reprints undated
Turner, Edward Raymond, 1881-1929.
1 box
7210 DA 2;T945;P186
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Edward Turner was professor of European history at the University of Michigan and other colleges and universities.
This collection of articles and reprints of articles written by Edward Turner was accumulated from different sources.
Subjects:
Abolitionists.; Great Britain--History.
- Pamphlets and reprints.
  - Are American school histories now too pro-British?, undated (Box 1)
  - The causes of the Great War. 1915 (Box 1)
  - Committees of council and the cabinet, 1660-1688. 1914 (Box 1)
  - Committees of the Privy Council, 1688-1760. 1916 (Box 1)
  - The development of the cabinet, 1688-1760. 1913 (Box 1)
  - The first Abolition Society in the United States. 1912 (Box 1)
  - The Hindu-Arabic numerals. 1912 (Box 1)
  - The keelmen of Newcastle. 1916 (Box 1)
  - The King's closet in the eighteenth century. 1940 (Box 1)
  - The Lords Justices of England 1695-1755. 1914 (Box 1)
  - Macaulay's 'History' illustrated. 1916 (Box 1)
  - The materials for the study of the English cabinet in the eighteenth century. 1913 (Box 1)
  - The Morocco crisis of 1911. 1912 (Box 1)
  - The privy council of 1679. 1913
  - The rivalry of Germany and England. 1913 (Box 1)
  - Women's suffrage in New Jersey, 1790-1807. 1916 (Box 1)
  - The Women's suffrage movement in England. 1913 (Box 1)